A Guide to the Robert James Sullivan Jr. Papers, ca. 1930-2013: SC 0003
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
Robert James Sullivan Jr. Papers,
ca. 1930-2013
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
Sullivan, Robert James, Jr., 1937-2013
SC 0003
8.53 cubic feet; 12 boxes, 4 flat files
The Robert James Sullivan Jr. Papers consist of professional and personal records and reports, and document Sullivan's time as City Planner of Harrisonburg from 1965-1991, his career in the Political Science Department at James Madison University, and work as the "unofficial historian" of Harrisonburg. Materials include city planning reports, newspaper articles, photographs, scrapbooks, and maps.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection open to research. Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection. Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the James Madison University Special Collections Library to use this collection.
Acquisition Information
The collection was donated by Kathleen Sullivan, wife of Robert James Sullivan Jr., in two separate donations in April 2014 and August 2015.
Other Formats Available
Materials within the Photographs and Slides series have been digitized and are available via JMU Scholarly Commons (https://commons.lib.jmu.edu/rjs/).
Bio/Historical Note
Robert "Bobby" James Sullivan Jr. was born on November 18, 1937 in Harrisonburg, Virginia and was the eldest son of the late Robert J. Sullivan Sr. and Goldie Liskey Sullivan. He passed away on February 4, 2013. Sullivan graduated from Harrisonburg High School in 1956 and received a Bachelor of Science degree from Mount St. Mary's College in 1960 and a master's degree in Public Administration from the University of Pittsburgh in 1962. He married Kathleen Marie Donovan on June 27, 1964.
Sullivan was the City Planner for the city of Harrisonburg from 1965-1991 during the years that saw Urban Redevelopment for parts of the city as well as growth through annexation. He also taught as an adjunct Assistant Professor of Political Science for James Madison University from 1970-2006. See folder titled "Background Information, Robert J. Sullivan, Jr., August 1998" from the Personal Papers series for details of his life and career.
Known locally as the "unofficial historian" of Harrisonburg, Sullivan often spoke to groups about the history of Harrisonburg. He was responsible for creating walking tours of downtown Harrisonburg first with his JMU Political Science classes, and later with the larger community.
Sullivan was a life-long member of Blessed Sacrament parish and a member of the Knights of Columbus. He served on the Rockingham Public Library Board and the Salvation Army Advisory Board for over thirty years. He was especially fond of the Harrisonburg High School athletic teams and was recognized as the Harrisonburg Blue Streaks biggest fan when he was inducted into the Harrisonburg High School Hall of Fame as part of the inaugural class of 2008.
Scope and Content
The Robert James Sullivan Jr. Papers consist of materials that Sullivan created and collected relating mostly to the city of Harrisonburg, Virginia, where he served as the City Planner from 1965-1991. The collection contains documents related to city planning, the history and expansion of Harrisonburg, and urban renewal. Other materials document his time in the Political Science Department at James Madison University as well as the walking tours he led of downtown Harrisonburg. His personal papers include newspaper clippings, correspondence, and other documents relating to his life and career. Also contained in the collection are a large number of photographs and slides that Sullivan took that capture the growth and changes in Harrisonburg over time. Images of note include a panoramic view of Harrisonburg ca. 1930, photos and slides that document urban renewal projects, and images of downtown Harrisonburg, VA from the 1960s-2000s.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in the following six series and subseries. All series and subseries arranged chronologically.
Series 1: Reports, 1946-1992
Subseries 1.1: City Planning Commission Annual Reports, 1966-1981
Subseries 1.2: Urban Planning Grants, 1965-1966
Subseries 1.3: Miscellaneous City Planning Reports, 1946-1992, undated
Series 2: City of Harrisonburg, 1958-2012
Subseries 2.1: City Planning, 1960-2012
Subseries 2.2: Harrisonburg History, 1958-2008
Series 3: Personal Papers, 1952-2013
Series 4: Scrapbooks and Newspaper, 1945-2012
Series 5: Maps, 1958-2003
Series 6: Photographs and Slides, ca. 1930-2012
Subseries 6.1: Photographs, ca. 1930-2012
Subseries 6.2: Slides, ca. 1965-1988
Related Material
SdArch no.2-3: Oral history interview [sound recording] / Bob Sullivan; interviewed by Amy Accles, forms part of Court Square, Harrisonburg, Virginia, an oral history project. Transcript also available in Special Collections and the general collection: F234.H31 A29 1990.
The Harrisonburg, VA branch of the Massanutten Regional Library holds 36 scrapbooks created by Sullivan from the years 1965-2001. These scrapbooks are cataloged under the title "Harrisonburg Civic Scrapbook."
Index Terms
Subjects:
Madison College -- Faculty; Madison College -- History; James Madison University -- Faculty; James Madison University -- History; City planning -- Virginia -- Harrisonburg; Community development, Urban -- Virginia -- Harrisonburg; Harrisonburg (Va.) -- History -- 20th century; Harrisonburg (Va.) -- History -- 21st century; Harrisonburg (Va.) -- Description and travel; Harrisonburg (Va.) -- Politics and government; Newtown (Rockingham County, Va.) -- History; Virginia -- History, Local
Genre and Form Terms:
Letters (correspondence); Color slides; Digital images; Photographs; Annual reports; Maps (documents); Newspaper clippings; Scrapbooks; Pamphlets; Drawings (visual works); Brochures
- Series 1: Reports, 1946-1992
  Scope and Content
  Arranged into three subseries: City Planning Commission Annual Reports, 1966-1981, Urban Planning Grants, 1965-1966, and Miscellaneous Reports, 1946-1992. Arranged chronologically within each series.
  - Subseries 1.1: City Planning Commission Annual Reports, 1966-1981
    Subseries 1.1: City Planning Commission Annual Reports, 1966-1981, contains a continuous run of annual reports for the City Planning Commission from 1965 through 1981. These annual reports include planning commission highlights and monthly summaries of activities. The 1965-1966 report notes that Robert J. Sullivan Jr. took over the duties of Planning Director on October 1, 1965.
    - Annual Report 1965-1966 Harrisonburg City Planning Commission, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Harrisonburg City Planning Commission Annual Report 1966-1967, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Harrisonburg City Planning Commission Annual Report 1967-'68, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Harrisonburg City Planning Commission 1968-'69 Annual Report, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Harrisonburg City Planning Commission 1969-1970 Annual Report, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - City of Harrisonburg, Virginia Planning Commission 1970-71 and 1971-72 Summary Report, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - City of Harrisonburg, Virginia 1972-1973 Planning Commission Summary Report, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - City of Harrisonburg, Virginia Planning Commission 1973-1974 Summary Report, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - City of Harrisonburg, Virginia Planning Commission 1974-1975 Summary Report, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - City of Harrisonburg, Virginia Planning Commission 1975-1976 Summary Report, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - City of Harrisonburg, Virginia Planning Commission 1976-1977 Summary Report, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - City of Harrisonburg, Virginia Planning Commission 1977-1978 Summary Report, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - City of Harrisonburg Planning Commission Summary Report 1978-1979, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - City of Harrisonburg, Virginia Planning Commission Summary Report 1979-1980, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Harrisonburg Planning Commission Summary Report for 1980-81 1980 City's Bicentennial, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 1.2: Urban Planning Grants, 1965-1966
    Subseries 1.2: Urban Planning Grants, 1965-1966, contains reports prepared under the contract for the Local Planning Section: Department of Conservation and Economic Development, State of Virginia. The preparation of these reports was funded in part through an urban planning grant from the Housing and Home Finance Agency. The reports contain analysis of various aspects of the city of Harrisonburg, including population statistics and information pertaining to residential neighborhoods and the downtown area. These Urban Planning Grants also include a 1966 comprehensive plan for development over the following twenty years as well as a summary report of that plan. These reports were office copies that belonged to Robert James Sullivan Jr. and have his name written on the cover. Because of excessive mold on these reports, all items from this subseries have been photocopied and originals discarded.
    - Urban Planning Grant: Project No. Va. P-9 Central Business District, Parking, Major Arterial Streets, Transportation and Transit Plans, November 1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Urban Planning Grant: Project No. Va. P-9 Economic Base, Population, and Land Use Analysis, May 1963, August 1965, November 1965, November 1965 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Urban Planning Grant: Project No. Va. P-9 Neighborhood Analysis, Harrisonburg, VA, November 1965 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Urban Planning Grant: Project No. Va. P-9 Preliminary Community Facilities and Land Use Plans, November 1965 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Urban Planning Grant: Project No. Va. P-9 Public Improvements Program, April 1966 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Urban Planning Grant: Project No. Va. P-9 Comprehensive Plan Harrisonburg, VA, June 1966 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Urban Planning Grant: Project No. Va. P-9 Comprehensive Plan Harrisonburg, VA, November 1966 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Subseries 1.3: Miscellaneous City Planning Reports, 1946-1992
    Subseries 1.3: Miscellaneous City Planning Reports, 1946-1992, contains various other reports that relate to city planning in Harrisonburg or city planning in general. Two reports relate to city planning in Norfolk, Virginia from the 1940s and 1950s and document urban renewal or "slum clearance" efforts there. Box 1 folder 27 contains an outline of the history of City Planning in Harrisonburg, beginning with the establishment of the Planning Commission in March, 1938. The report titled Harrisonburg: "The City with the Planned Future," contains a detailed history of the founding and growth of Harrisonburg, including population statistics and documentation of land annexation as well a listing of the members of City Council from 1849-2006.
    - This Is It Booklet, Norfolk, VA, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Downtown Construction, Remodeling, and Demolition Records 1955, 1955-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Rebirth of a City, Norfolk, VA Official Publication of the Norfolk Chamber of Commerce, September 1959 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Master Plan for the Central Shenandoah Valley Region Sociology Pro-Seminar Term Paper 1960 Spring Semester Robert J Sullivan Jr., 1960 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Focus on Harrisonburg's Central Business District, July 1967 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - The Development of City Planning in Harrisonburg by Robert J. Sullivan Jr., April 1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Commercial, Professional, Religious and Governmental Establishments in Harrisonburg, VA, November 1990 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - City of Harrisonburg 1991 Comprehensive Plan, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Harrisonburg: "The City with the Planned Future", undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Planning Sector Analysis, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Series 2: City of Harrisonburg, 1958-2012
  Arranged into two subseries: City Planning, 1960-2012, and Harrisonburg History, 1958-2008. Arranged chronologically within each series.
  - Subseries 2.1: City Planning, 1960-2012
    Subseries 2.1: City Planning, 1960-2012, contains materials that Sullivan created in his role as City Planner, or that relate to city planning functions. Types of materials include photos and other documents related to the Northeast Urban Redevelopment Project, newspaper articles about city planning and the growth and development of Harrisonburg, and documents relating to zoning and historic district status. The folders titled "What do you think of Federal Aid? Photos and description," contain a document written in 2012 by Sullivan explaining the history of urban redevelopment in Harrisonburg, and his role in the "slum clearance" projects of the 1950s and 1960s.
    - Photograph: Aerial View of Harrisonburg: Spotswood under Construction, 1960 (Mapcase 3, Drawer 8, Folder 4)
    - What do you think of Federal Aid? Photos and description (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1960, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - What do you think of Federal Aid? Photos and description (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1960, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Newspaper Articles – City Planning, 1967, 1972, 1976, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Parks and Recreation Master Plan, Harrisonburg VA 1st Revision, January 24, 1968 (Box OV 1, Folder 1a)
    - "Talmadge R. Cooley, Harrisonburg Civic Leader," by Robert J. Sullivan Jr., ca. 1971 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Aerial View of Harrisonburg, 1972, undated (Box OV 1, Folder 1b)
    - Harrisonburg Area Transportation Study (HATS)-Includes Year 2015 Plan, 1979-1999 (Box 1, Folder 34, Mapcase 3, Drawer 8, Folder 4)
    - VCPA Conference May 18-20 1986, 1986, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Harrisonburg Growth Articles August – September, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Harrisonburg Comprehensive Plan Update 1997 (Historic Background Section) – includes info on Historic District Status, 1991-2002 (Box 3, Folder 3, Box OV 1, Folder 1c)
    - Old Town Harrisonburg Rezoning Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 4, Box OV 1, Folder 1d)
  - Subseries 2.2: Harrisonburg History, 1958-2008
    Subseries 2.2: Harrisonburg History, 1958-2008, contains materials collected by Sullivan that relate to the history of Harrisonburg, as well as materials he created related to the history and development of the city. Sullivan was known as the "unofficial historian of Harrisonburg" and materials in this subseries document the history and development of Harrisonburg. Items of note include original drawings of downtown Harrisonburg from the 1950s and 1960s as well as posters and brochures that contain Sullivan's sketches for the 1980 Bicentennial celebration. Other materials include the text of various talks Sullivan gave on the history of Harrisonburg to various groups in town.
    - Original Drawings of Downtown Harrisonburg by Robert J. Sullivan Jr., 1958 (Box OV 1, Folder 2)
    - My Recollections of Rocktown Now Known as Harrisonburg by Maria G. Carr, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Chronology of Harrisonburg, ca. 1962 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Original Drawing: Old Spring House on the Court Square – To be reconstructed in time for Harrisonburg's 200th Anniversary, 1966 (Mapcase 3, Drawer 8, Folder 4)
    - Historic Harrisonburg Virginia – A Walking Tour, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Walking Tour of Downtown/Journey into the Past Brochures and Fliers, 1976, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - "Harrisonburg"— Article from Shenandoah Valley Magazine, August 1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - "Harrisonburg Bicentennial Ecumenical Celebration of Faith" program, July 3, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Bicentennial Envelope, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Journey into the Past: Historic Harrisonburg Bicentennial Poster, 1980 (Mapcase 3, Drawer 8, Folder 4)
    - Journey into the Past: Historic Harrisonburg Sketches/Bicentennial Harrisonburg Sketches, 1980, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - "Harrisonburg Celebrates its Bicentennial", ca. 1980 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Harrisonburg: The Transformation of a City – A Photographic exhibit arranged by Martha Caldwell, Caroline Marshall and Mike Zirkle, ca. 1980 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Valley National Bank Brochure with Harrisonburg photos, ca. 1980 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Ephemera Harrisonburg History, 1980, 1993, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Downtown Brochures, 1984, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Journey into the Past: A Walking Tour of Harrisonburg, VA, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Harrisonburg-Rockingham Historical Society Newsletter – A Brief History of Harrisonburg by Robert J. Sullivan Jr., 1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Upstream Magazine: "Fred Cooper: Harrisonburg's Sketch Pad Preservationist", 1990 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - "A Few Facts about Harrisonburg" Talk to Rotary Club, July 26, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Check-It-Out-Rockingham Public Library Newsletter, Austin Loewner article, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Maps of Harrisonburg for Phone Directory, 1993-1994, 2003, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Common Ground Vol. VII No. 8 Article Written by Robert J. Sullivan Jr., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Harrisonburg "Blue Streaks" Football History Booklet by Robert J. Sullivan Jr., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Articles and Maps about Downtown Harrisonburg, 1994, 1999, 2003, 2008, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - "Spring House", 1995, undated (Box 3, Folder 27, Box OV 1, Folder 1e)
    - Harrisonburg – copies of photos with descriptions 1960s-1990s, ca. 1995 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - DNR –"A Walk Through History", April 1996 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - AARP Talk about Harrisonburg, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Newspaper: "Your hometown…Bridgewater" clippings, February 14, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - DNR – Harrisonburg Growth Articles, July 2 – July 7, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - 2002 Downtown Walk for Library Friends, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Historic District Status DNR, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Spotswood Elementary School Drawings, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - City Produce Exchange/Wetsel Seed Co. by Robert E. Wetsel, August 2006 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Old Town Historic District, 2006, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Massanutten Regional Library – The Deyerle Programs: An Artist's Visual Snapshot of Harrisonburg, ca. 2006 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Harrisonburg-Rockingham Historical Society Newsletter – Emma Lyon Bryan painting, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Harrisonburg Downtown Renaissance membership ephemera, undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Harrisonburg Downtown Renaissance: Walking Tour Brochure, undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Harrisonburg, 1959 photo album [no photos, description only], undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Historic Postcards, undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - National Hotel – image from 1958-59 Photo Album, undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Notes on Harrisonburg – streets, buildings, etc., undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Rockingham County Courthouse, image pre-1896, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Valley National Bank Presents Harrisonburg Illustrations by Austin Loewner, text by John Green, undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Series 3: Personal Papers, 1952-2013
  Arranged Chronologically. Materials in the Personal Papers series document Sullivan's professional activities as well as his time as an instructor in the Political Science Department at James Madison University. Please note that the folder titled "JMU Classes - Evaluations," do not contain student grades or performance evaluations, but rather contain evaluations completed by students about Sullivan's performance as an instructor. For details of Sullivan's life and career highlights please see the folder titled "Background Information Robert J. Sullivan Jr., August 1998."
  - Articles about Robert J. Sullivan Jr., 1952-2003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Personal Property Plans, 1961, 1967 (Box OV 1, Folder 3)
  - DNR Article – Sullivan Named as Director of City Planning Commission, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - JMU General Catalogs with Sullivan listed as instructor, 1970-1977 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Letters to the Editor by RJS, 1974-2003 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - DNR Article – Sullivan Knows Every Inch of Harrisonburg, February 15, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Personal Letters, 1989, 1993, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Personal Letters, Robert J. Sullivan Jr. (folder 1 of 2), 1995-2005 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Personal Letters, Robert J. Sullivan Jr. (folder 2 of 2), 1995-2005 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Background Information Robert J. Sullivan Jr., August 1998 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - "Harrisonburg, Louisiana," Term Paper for Posc. 302, For Professor Sullivan's State and Local Government Class, and DNR Article, 2002, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - JMU Classes - Evaluations, 2003-2006, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - JMU All Together One Recognition, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Spring Semester POSC 302 Class Information (folder 1 of 2), 2004-2006, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Spring Semester POSC 302 Class Information (folder 2 of 2), 2004-2006, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Health Articles, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Distinguished Public Service Award, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - May 6, 2009 Article on Bob Sullivan's Scrapbooks, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - RJS Obituary and Joint Resolution Celebrating the life of Robert James Sullivan Jr., 2013 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Series 4: Scrapbooks and Newspaper, 1945-2012
  Arranged Chronologically. The Scrapbooks and Newspaper series consists of newspaper clippings, either loose in folders, or pasted into scrapbooks, that document city planning and growth primarily in Harrisonburg, VA. Most newspaper clipping come from the Daily News-Record, the local newspaper for Harrisonburg, Virginia. In addition to clippings that document city planning efforts, Sullivan also collected clippings that relate to historical aspects of Harrisonburg, particularly those that feature images of Harrisonburg from the past. The folder titled "News and Photos from DNR - "Old Times," contains a copy of the front page of the Daily News-Record from 1945 that reports on the ending of World War II. Please note that the scrapbooks in box 5, folders 4-7 are photocopies of the original scrapbooks. The original scrapbooks suffered from mold damage and were not retained.
  - News and Photos from DNR – "Old Times", 1945-1995, undated (Box OV 1, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1959-1989 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Clippings – Harrisonburg Development, 1960-2000, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - DNR Images of Old Time Harrisonburg, 1960-2004, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook - City of Harrisonburg, Virginia September 1955 thru Fall of 1957, 1955-1957 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook - City Planning Commission: Redevelopment and Housing Authority Newspaper Clippings, 1957-1961 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook - Harrisonburg Planning Commission News Clippings, 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook - Richmond, Virginia City Planning Newspaper Clippings, 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Harrisonburg Maps from Newspapers, 1975-2002, undated (Box OV 1, Folder 5)
  - DNR and The Breeze Special Issues, 1979-1999, undated (Box OV 1, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1990-1999 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 2000-2010 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbooked DNR Newspaper Clippings, July 2001 – October 2001 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbooked DNR Newspaper Clippings, October 2001 – March 2002 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbooked DNR Newspaper Clippings, March 2002 – May 2002 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbooked DNR Newspaper Clippings, May 2002 – August 2002 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Daily News-Record, August 2002 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Daily News-Record, September 2002 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Daily News-Record, October 2002 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Daily News-Record, November 2002 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Daily News-Record, December 2002 (Box 6, Folder 5)